goodreturns.in 2012-06-22

# Oneindia | Privacy Policy

Home » Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

Oneindia.in Privacy Policy describes how we maintain your personal information when you register for Oneindia.in's services which include Oneindia Mail, Oneindia Bookmarks, Oneindia Videos, Oneindia Blogs, Public Notice & Fans Community on <http://popcorn.oneindia.in/> .

**Personal information**

  * You will need to create a [Oneindia Accoun](http://user.oneindia.in/)t to use the services on Oneindia.in. Oneindia.in will collect personal information when you create your Account which includes your email address, your name and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. The Oneindia Account allows you to access all of our services including Oneindia Mail, Oneindia Bookmarks, Oneindia Videos, Oneindia Blogs, Public Notice, Fans community.
  * As a Fan Club member, you can create a profile which includes personal information, such as your name (if no nickname is set), gender, location and also add profile photo. This information may be accessed and viewed by other members.
  * When you invite new members into your network or send messages through the Fan Club, Oneindia.in collects and maintains the email addresses associated with the messages.

**Uses and Information Sharing**

  * Oneindia.in maintains and processes your personal information and content of your communications in order to provide access to Oneindia services and the use of Fan Club services. 
  * Your profile information displayed on your Fan Club account includes you name (if no nickname is set), gender, location and date of joining the Fan Club. 
  * When you send messages through the Fan Club, your name and email address will be identified in the message. We also use your name and email address to notify you of new members, messages and or other information, such as invitations to join fan clubs, new alerts including ratings, reviews, recommendations, and crush notices. 
  * If you invite another person or friends to join the Fan Club, we use the name and email address you provide us to contact that person and, if necessary, may send reminders to join. 
  * Friends or other persons can search your profile by using the nickname provided in your profile. 
  * Oneindia.in allows you to upload photos & videos to your profile. You understand that Photos & Videos posted are the sole responsibility of the person/user from which such content originated and such content are publicly available for other users to see, rate, recommend and download.
  * Users may also post reviews, comments, polls, quizzes, so long as the contents are not illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights, or otherwise injurious to third parties or objectionable and not contain political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of "spam". 
  * Oneindia.in pre-screens user submitted polls & quizzes, the right to approve, reject or remove such content solely remains with Oneindia.in.
  * You agree not to submit material that is copyrighted, protected by trade secret or otherwise subject to third party proprietary rights, including privacy and publicity rights, unless you are the owner of such rights or have written permission from their rightful owner to post the material and to grant Oneindia.in all of the license rights granted herein.

**Your Fan Club Profile**

  * Oneindia.in allows you to view and share your information with your friends, friends of friends and all Fan Club members.
  * You can update your profile information anytime by clicking on the "edit" on your profile.
  * Messages from Oneindia.in or your friends will be sent to your Primary email address provided while registering for Oneindia.in Account.

**Advertisers**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

**Disclaimer**

We value the privacy of information pertaining to its associates. We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to our portal.

We will not use information about you without your permission and will provide the means for you to manage and control the information that you have provided. You agree to receive promotional communications from us (email and/or SMS) unless you specifically indicate otherwise in writing to us.

We do not disclose any personal information to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes that could be used to personally identify you, such as your password, credit card number and bank account number. 

**More information**

Our Terms & Condition, Privacy Policy and other related legal information applies to all sites owned by the Company. If you have additional questions, please write to [inquiries@greynium.com](mailto:inquiries@greynium.com)
